Finding Aid to The Georgia O'Keeffe Foundation Photographs MS.57
Georgia O'Keeffe Museum
- Georgia O'Keeffe's Abiquiu House, Aerial View, 1979; 2006.6.469; Mang, Fred E., Jr., b. 1923; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 7 15/16 x 10 inches; Handwritten on verso: Georgia O'Keeffe Home NPS Photo By Fred Mang Jr.; Stamp on verso: Print Made By Kodak May 1980Stamp on verso: Kodak Apr 79; Handwritten on verso:'79-199-1 Georgia O'Keeffe Home NPS Photo By Fred Mang Jr.'
- Georgia O'Keeffe's Abiquiu House, Aerial View, 1979; 2006.6.470; Mang, Fred E., Jr., b. 1923; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 7 15/16 x 10 inches; Handwritten on verso: Georgia O'Keeffe Home NPS Photo By Fred Mang Jr.; Stamp on verso: Print Made By Kodak May 1980Stamp on verso: Kodak Apr 79; Handwritten on verso: '79-199-3 Georgia O'Keeffe Home NPS Photo By Fred Mang Jr.'
- Georgia O'Keeffe's Abiquiu House, Aerial View, 1979; 2006.6.471; Mang, Fred E., Jr., b. 1923; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 10 x 8 1/8 inches; Handwritten on verso: Georgia O'Keeffe, SWRO; Stamp on verso: US Department of Interior National Park Service Photo By Fred Mang, Jr.Stamp on verso: US Department of Interior National Park Service Photo By Fred Mang Jr. Handwritten on verso: "GEORGIA O'KEEFFE. SWRO 16 A-17" "MANG 9"
- Georgia O'Keeffe's Abiquiu House, Aerial View, 1979; 2006.6.472; Mang, Fred E., Jr., b. 1923; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 8 3/16 x 10 inches; Handwritten on verso: Georgia O'Keeffe, SWRO; Stamp on verso: US Department of Interior National Park Service Photo By Fred Mang, Jr.Stamp on verso: US Department of Interior National Park Service Photo By Fred Mang Jr. Handwriting on verso: "GEORGIA O'KEEFFE, SWRO 16A-17" "MANG 9" "SWRO 79-102/24A-25"
- Georgia O'Keeffe's Abiquiu House, Aerial View, 1979; 2006.6.473; Mang, Fred E., Jr., b. 1923; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 7 15/16 x 10 inches; Handwritten on verso: Georgia O'Keeffe, SWRO; Stamp on verso: US Department of Interior National Park Service Photo By Fred Mang, Jr.Stamp on verso: US Department of Interior National Park Service Photo By Fred Mang Jr. Handwriting on verso: "GEORGIA O'KEEFFE SWRO 79-102 FRAME 24A-25" "MANG 10" "SWRO 79-102/24A-25"
- Georgia O'Keeffe's Abiquiu House, Aerial View, 1979; 2006.6.474; Mang, Fred E., Jr., b. 1923; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 8 1/8 x 10 inches; Handwritten on verso: Georgia O'Keeffe, SWRO; Stamp on verso: US Department of Interior National Park Service Photo By Fred Mang, Jr.Stamp on verso: US Department of Interior National Park Service Photo By Fred Mang Jr. Handwriting on verso: "GEORGIA O'KEEFFE, SWRO 28A-29" "MANG 11"
- Georgia O'Keeffe's Abiquiu House, Aerial View, 1979; 2006.6.475; Mang, Fred E., Jr., b. 1923; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 8 1/8 x 10 inches; Handwritten on verso: Georgia O'Keeffe, SWRO; Stamp on verso: US Department of Interior National Park Service Photo By Fred Mang, Jr.Stamp on verso: US Department of Interior National Park Service Photo By Fred Mang Jr. Handwriting on verso: "GEORGIA O'KEEFFE, SWRO 29-30" "MANG 12"
- Georgia O'Keeffe's Abiquiu House, Aerial View, 1979; 2006.6.476; Mang, Fred E., Jr., b. 1923; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 7 15/16 x 9 15/16 inches; Handwritten on verso: Georgia O'Keeffe, SWRO; Stamp on verso: US Department of Interior National Park Service Photo By Fred Mang, Jr.Stamp on verso: US Department of Interior National Park Service Photo By Fred Mang Jr. Handwriting on verso: "GEORGIA O'KEEFFE, SWRO 79-102 FRAME 34A 35" "34A-35" "MANG 13"
- Georgia O'Keeffe's Abiquiu House, Patio, 1979; 2006.6.477; Mang, Fred E., Jr., b. 1923; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 7 7/8 x 10 inches; Stamp on verso: US Department of Interior National Park Service Photo By Fred Mang, Jr. Kodak Mar 1979; Handwritten on verso: 79-49-12Stamp on verso: 'US Department of Interior National Park Service Photo By Fred Mang Jr.'; Stamp on verso: Kodak Mar 79; Handwritten on verso:'79-49-12 / mang 14'
- Georgia O'Keeffe's Abiquiu House, Exterior Main Gate, 1979; 2006.6.478; Mang, Fred E., Jr., b. 1923; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 7 15/16 x 10 inches; Stamp on verso: US Department of Interior National Park Service Photo By Fred Mang, Jr. Kodak Feb 1979; Handwritten on verso: 79-49-14Stamp on verso: 'US Department of Interior National Park Service Photo By Fred Mang Jr.'; stamp on verso: Kodak Feb 79; Handwritten on verso '79-49-14 mang 15'
- Georgia O'Keeffe's Abiquiu House, Exterior Sitting Room, 1979; 2006.6.479; Mang, Fred E., Jr., b. 1923; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 7 15/16 x 10 inches; Stamp on verso: US Department of Interior National Park Service Photo By Fred Mang, Jr. Kodak Feb 1979; Handwritten on verso: 79-49-15Stamp on verso: 'US Department of Interior National Park Service Photo By Fred Mang Jr.'; Stamp on verso: Kodak Feb 79; Handwritten on verso: '79-49-15 mang 16'
- Georgia O'Keeffe's Abiquiu House, Exterior Parking, 1979; 2006.6.480; Mang, Fred E., Jr., b. 1923; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 7 15/16 x 10 inches; Stamp on verso: US Department of Interior National Park Service Photo By Fred Mang, Jr. Kodak Feb 1979; Handwritten on verso: Entrance to parking area 79-49-16Stamp on verso: 'US Department of Interior National Park Service Photo By Fred Mang Jr.'; Stamp on verso: Kodak Feb 79; Handwritten on verso:'Entrance to Parking Area, 79-49-16, mang 17'
- Georgia O'Keeffe's Abiquiu House, Exterior Main Door, 1979; 2006.6.481; Mang, Fred E., Jr., b. 1923; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 7 15/16 x 10 inches; Stamp on verso: Kodak Feb 1979; Handwritten on verso: 79-49-19Stamp on verso: Kodak Feb 79; Handwritten on verso: '79-49-19 mang 18'
- Georgia O'Keeffe's Abiquiu House, Zaguan, 1979; 2006.6.482; Mang, Fred E., Jr., b. 1923; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 10 x 7 15/16 inches; Stamp on verso: Kodak Mar 1979; Handwritten on verso: 79-49-20Stamp on verso: Kodak Mar 79; Handwritten on verso: '79-49-20'
- Georgia O'Keeffe's Abiquiu House, Hallway, 1979; 2006.6.483; Mang, Fred E., Jr., b. 1923; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 10 x 7 15/16 inches; Stamp on verso: Kodak Feb 1979; Handwritten on verso: 79-49-21Stamp on verso: Kodak Feb 79; Handwritten on verso: '79-49-21 Mang 20'
- Georgia O'Keeffe's Abiquiu House, Exterior, 1979; 2006.6.484; Mang, Fred E., Jr., b. 1923; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 7 15/16 x 10 inches; Stamp on verso: Kodak Feb 1979; Handwritten on verso: 79-49-22Stamp on verso: Kodak Feb 79; Handwritten on verso: '79-49-22, Mang 21'
- Georgia O'Keeffe's Abiquiu House, Patio, 1979; 2006.6.485; Mang, Fred E., Jr., b. 1923; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 7 15/16 x 9 15/16 inches; Stamp on verso: Kodak Feb 1979; Handwritten on verso: 79-49-23Stamp on verso: Kodak Feb 79; Handwritten on verso: '79-49-23 Mang 22'
- Georgia O'Keeffe's Abiquiu House, Exterior, 1979; 2006.6.486; Mang, Fred E., Jr., b. 1923; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 7 15/16 x 10 inches; Stamp on verso: Kodak Feb 1979; Handwritten on verso: 79-49-25Stamp on verso: Kodak Feb 79; Handwritten on verso: '79-49-25 Mang 23'
- Georgia O'Keeffe's Abiquiu House, Exterior and Garden, 1979; 2006.6.487; Mang, Fred E., Jr., b. 1923; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 7 15/16 x 10 inches; Stamp on verso: Kodak Feb 1979; Handwritten on verso: O'Keeffe 79-49-29Stamp on verso: Kodak Feb 79; Handwritten on verso: '79-49-29 O'Keeffe Mang 24'
- Georgia O'Keeffe's Abiquiu House, Exterior and Ladder, 1979; 2006.6.488; Mang, Fred E., Jr., b. 1923; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 7 15/16 x 10 inches; Stamp on verso: Kodak Feb 1979; Handwritten on verso: O'Keeffe 79-49-30Stamp on verso: Kodak Feb 79; Handwritten on verso: '79-49-30 O'Keeffe Mang 25'
- Georgia O'Keeffe's Abiquiu House, Exterior and Garden, 1979; 2006.6.489; Mang, Fred E., Jr., b. 1923; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 7 15/16 x 10 inches; Stamp on verso: US Department of Interior National Park Service Photo By Fred Mang, Jr. Kodak Feb 1979; Handwritten on verso: 79-49-31Stamp on verso: 'US Department of Interior National Park Service Photo By Fred Mang Jr.'; Stamp on verso: Kodak Feb 79; Handwritten on verso: '79-49-31 mang 26'
- Georgia O'Keeffe's Abiquiu House, Living Room, 1979; 2006.6.490; Mang, Fred E., Jr., b. 1923; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 7 15/16 x 10 inches; Stamp on verso: US Department of Interior National Park Service Photo By Fred Mang, Jr. Kodak Feb 1979; Handwritten on verso: 79-49-9Stamp on verso: 'US Department of Interior National Park Service Photo By Fred Mang Jr.'; Stamp on verso: Kodak Feb 79; Handwritten on verso: '79-49-9 mang 42'
- Georgia O'Keeffe's Abiquiu House, Living Room, 1979; 2006.6.491; Mang, Fred E., Jr., b. 1923; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 7 15/16 x 10 inches; Stamp on verso: US Department of Interior National Park Service Photo By Fred Mang, Jr. Kodak Feb 1979; Handwritten on verso: 79-49-7Stamp on verso: 'US Department of Interior National Park Service Photo By Fred Mang Jr.'; stamp on verso: Kodak Feb 79; Handwritten on verso: '79-49-7 mang 40'
- Georgia O'Keeffe's Abiquiu House, Fireplace, 1979; 2006.6.492; Mang, Fred E., Jr., b. 1923; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 10 x 7 15/16 inches; Stamp on verso: Kodak Mar 1979; Handwritten on verso: 79-49-5Stamp on verso: Kodak Mar 79; Handwritten on verso: '79-49-5 Mang 38'
- Georgia O'Keeffe's Abiquiu House, Dining and Living Room, 1979; 2006.6.493; Mang, Fred E., Jr., b. 1923; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 7 15/16 x 9 15/16 inches; Stamp on verso: US Department of Interior National Park Service Photo By Fred Mang, Jr. Kodak Feb 1979; Handwritten on verso: 79-49-78Stamp on verso: 'US Department of Interior National Park Service Photo By Fred Mang Jr.'; stamp on verso Kodak Feb 79; Handwritten on verso: '79-49-78 mang 51'
- Georgia O'Keeffe's Abiquiu House, Living Room Fireplace, 1979; 2006.6.494; Mang, Fred E., Jr., b. 1923; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 7 15/16 x 10 inches; Stamp on verso: Kodak Feb 1979; Handwritten on verso: 79-49-24Stamp on verso: Kodak Feb 79; Handwritten on verso: '79-49-24 Mang 48'
- Georgia O'Keeffe's Abiquiu House, Living Room, 1979; 2006.6.495; Mang, Fred E., Jr., b. 1923; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 7 15/16 x 10 inches; Stamp on verso: Kodak Feb 1979; Handwritten on verso: 79-49-4Stamp on verso: Kodak Feb 79; Handwritten on verso: '79-49-4 Mang 37'
- Georgia O'Keeffe's Abiquiu House, Kitchen, 1979; 2006.6.496; Mang, Fred E., Jr., b. 1923; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 7 15/16 x 10 inches; Stamp on verso: US Department of Interior National Park Service Photo By Fred Mang, Jr. Kodak Feb 1979; Handwritten on verso: 79-49-2Stamp on verso: 'US Department of Interior National Park Service Photo By Fred Mang Jr.'; stamp on verso: Kodak Feb 79; Handwritten on verso: '79-49-2 mang 36'
- Georgia O'Keeffe's Abiquiu House, 1979; 2006.6.497; Mang, Fred E., Jr., b. 1923; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 7 7/8 x 10 1/16 inches; Stamp on verso: US Department of Interior National Park Service Photo By Fred Mang, Jr. Kodak Mar 1979; Handwritten on verso: 79-49-1Stamp on verso: 'US Department of Interior National Park Service Photo By Fred Mang Jr.'; stamp on verso: Kodak Mar 79; Handwritten on verso: '79-49-1 mang 35'
- Georgia O'Keeffe's Abiquiu House, Juan Hamilton in Studio, 1979; 2006.6.498; Mang, Fred E., Jr., b. 1923; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 8 x 10 inches; Handwritten on verso: 79-48-5Handwritten on verso: '79-48-5 mang 34'
- Georgia O'Keeffe's Abiquiu House, Studio, 1979; 2006.6.499; Mang, Fred E., Jr., b. 1923; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 7 15/16 x 10 inches; Stamp on verso: Kodak Mar 1979; Handwritten on verso: 79-49-6Stamp on verso: Kodak Mar 79; Handwritten on verso: '79-49-6 Mang 39'
- Georgia O'Keeffe's Abiquiu House, Studio Detail of Paintings by O'Keeffe, 1979; 2006.6.500; Mang, Fred E., Jr., b. 1923; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 7 15/16 x 10 inches; Stamp on verso: US Department of Interior National Park Service Photo By Fred Mang, Jr. Kodak Feb 1979; Handwritten on verso: 79-49-27Stamp on verso: 'US Department of Interior National Park Service Photo By Fred Mang Jr.'; stamp on verso: Kodak Feb 79; Handwritten on verso: '79-49-27 mang 50'
- Georgia O'Keeffe's Abiquiu House, Front Office, 1979; 2006.6.501; Mang, Fred E., Jr., b. 1923; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 7 15/16 x 10 inches; Stamp on verso: US Department of Interior National Park Service Photo By Fred Mang, Jr. Kodak Feb 1979; Handwritten on verso: 79-49-10Stamp on verso: 'US Department of Interior National Park Service Photo By Fred Mang Jr.'; stamp on verso: Kodak Feb 79; Handwritten on verso: '79-49-10 mang 43'
- Georgia O'Keeffe's Abiquiu House, Studio, 1979; 2006.6.502; Mang, Fred E., Jr., b. 1923; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 7 15/16 x 9 15/16 inches; Stamp on verso: US Department of Interior National Park Service Photo By Fred Mang, Jr.; Handwritten on verso: 79-49-26Stamp on verso: 'US Department of Interior National Park Service Photo By Fred Mang Jr.'; Handwritten on verso: '79-49-26 mang 49'
- Georgia O'Keeffe's Abiquiu House, Studio, 1979; 2006.6.503; Mang, Fred E., Jr., b. 1923; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 7 7/8 x 10 inches; Stamp on verso: US Department of Interior National Park Service Photo By Fred Mang, Jr. Kodak Mar 1979; Handwritten on verso: 79-49-13Stamp on verso: 'US Department of Interior National Park Service Photo By Fred Mang Jr.'; stamp on verso: Kodak Mar 79; Handwritten on verso: '79-49-13 mang 45'
- Georgia O'Keeffe's Abiquiu House, Bedroom, 1979; 2006.6.504; Mang, Fred E., Jr., b. 1923; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 7 7/8 x 10 inches; Stamp on verso: US Department of Interior National Park Service Photo By Fred Mang, Jr. Kodak Feb 1979; Handwritten on verso: 79-49-17Stamp on verso: 'US Department of Interior National Park Service Photo By Fred Mang Jr.'; Stamp on verso: Kodak Feb 79; Handwritten on verso: '79-49-17 mang 46'
- Georgia O'Keeffe's Abiquiu House, Bedroom, 1979; 2006.6.505; Mang, Fred E., Jr., b. 1923; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 7 7/8 x 10 inches; Stamp on verso: US Department of Interior National Park Service Photo By Fred Mang, Jr. Kodak Feb 1979; Handwritten on verso: 79-49-8Stamp on verso: 'US Department of Interior National Park Service Photo By Fred Mang Jr.'; Stamp on verso: Kodak Feb 79; Handwritten on verso: '79-49-8 mang 41'
- Georgia O'Keeffe's Abiquiu House, Bookroom, 1979; 2006.6.506; Mang, Fred E., Jr., b. 1923; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 10 x 7 15/16 inches; Stamp on verso: US Department of Interior National Park Service Photo By Fred Mang, Jr. Kodak Feb 1979; Handwritten on verso: 79-49-18Stamp on verso: 'US Department of Interior National Park Service Photo By Fred Mang Jr.'; Stamp on verso: Kodak Feb 79; Handwritten on verso: '79-49-18 mang 47'
- Georgia O'Keeffe's Abiquiu House, Living Room, 1979; 2006.6.507; Mang, Fred E., Jr., b. 1923; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 7 15/16 x 10 inches; Handwritten on verso: 1/23/79; Stamp on verso: US Department of Interior National Park Service Photo By Fred Mang, Jr.Stamp on verso: US Department of Interior National Park Service Photo By Fred Mang Jr. Handwriting on verso: "1/23/79" "MANG 54"
- Georgia O'Keeffe's Abiquiu House, Living Room, 1979; 2006.6.508; Mang, Fred E., Jr., b. 1923; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 7 15/16 x 10 inches; Handwritten on verso: 1/23/79; Stamp on verso: US Department of Interior National Park Service Photo By Fred Mang, Jr.Stamp on verso: US Department of Interior National Park Service Photo By Fred Mang Jr. Handwriting on verso: "1/23/79" "MANG 53"
- Georgia O'Keeffe's Abiquiu House, Patio, 1979; 2006.6.509; Mang, Fred E., Jr., b. 1923; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 7 15/16 x 9 15/16 inches; Handwritten on verso: 1/23/79; Stamp on verso: US Department of Interior National Park Service Photo By Fred Mang, Jr.Handwritten on verso: "1/23/79" "MANG 27"
- Georgia O'Keeffe's Abiquiu House, Exterior, 1979; 2006.6.510; Mang, Fred E., Jr., b. 1923; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 7 15/16 x 10 inches; Handwritten on verso: 1/23/79; Stamp on verso: US Department of Interior National Park Service Photo By Fred Mang, Jr.Stamp on verso: US Department of Interior National Park Service Photo By Fred Mang Jr. Handwriting on verso: "1/23/79" "MANG 28"
- Georgia O'Keeffe's Abiquiu House, Exterior, 1979; 2006.6.511; Mang, Fred E., Jr., b. 1923; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 7 15/16 x 10 inches; Handwritten on verso: 1/23/79; Stamp on verso: US Department of Interior National Park Service Photo By Fred Mang, Jr.Stamp on verso: US Department of Interior National Park Service Photo By Fred Mang Jr. Handwriting on verso: "1/23/79" "MANG 29"
- Georgia O'Keeffe's Abiquiu House, Exterior Main Door, 1979; 2006.6.512; Mang, Fred E., Jr., b. 1923; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 7 15/16 x 10 inches; Handwritten on verso: 1/23/79; Stamp on verso: US Department of Interior National Park Service Photo By Fred Mang, Jr.Stamp on verso: US Department of Interior National Park Service Photo By Fred Mang Jr. Handwriting on verso: "1/23/79" "MANG 31"
- Georgia O'Keeffe's Abiquiu House, Exterior Main Door, 1979; 2006.6.513; Mang, Fred E., Jr., b. 1923; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 7 15/16 x 9 15/16 inches; Handwritten on verso: 1/23/79; Stamp on verso: US Department of Interior National Park Service Photo By Fred Mang, Jr.Stamp on verso: US Department of Interior National Park Service Photo By Fred Mang Jr. Handwriting on verso: "1/23/79" "MANG 30"
- Georgia O'Keeffe's Abiquiu House, Roofless Room, 1980; 2006.6.514; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 7 15/16 x 10 inches; Polaroid copy.Handwritten on verso: 'Nichols 86'
  In Architectural Digest July 1981.
  Copyright Mary E. Nichols
- Georgia O'Keeffe's Abiquiu House, Living Room, 1980; 2006.6.515; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 7 15/16 x 10 inches; Polaroid copy.Handwritten on verso: 'Nichols 6b'
- Georgia O'Keeffe's Abiquiu House, Indian Room, 1980; 2006.6.516; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 10 x 7 15/16 inches; Polaroid copy.Handwritten on verso: 'Nichols 5b'
- Georgia O'Keeffe's Abiquiu House, Studio Bed, 1980; 2006.6.517; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 7 15/16 x 10 1/16 inches; Polaroid copy.Handwritten on verso: 'Nichols 9b'
- Georgia O'Keeffe's Abiquiu House, Studio with Painting and Sculpture, 1980; 2006.6.518; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 10 1/8\ x 7 15/16 inches; Polaroid copy.Handwritten on verso: 'Nichols 10b'
- Georgia O'Keeffe's Abiquiu House, Bedroom, 1980; 2006.6.519; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 7 15/16 x 9 15/16 inches; Polaroid copy.Handwritten on verso: 'Nichols 11b'
- Georgia O'Keeffe's Abiquiu House, Patio, 1980; 2006.6.520; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 10 x 7 15/16 inches; Polaroid copy.Handwritten on verso: 'Nichols 12b'
- Georgia O'Keeffe's Abiquiu House, Salita Door, 1980; 2006.6.521; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 10 x 7 15/16 inches; Polaroid copy.Handwritten on verso: 'Nichols 13b'
- Georgia O'Keeffe's Abiquiu House, Zaguan Door Exterior, 1980; 2006.6.522; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 7 15/16 x 10 1/16 inches; Polaroid copy.Handwritten on verso: 'Nichols 14b'
- Georgia O'Keeffe's Abiquiu House, Driveway and Gate, 1980; 2006.6.523; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 7 15/16 x 10 1/16 inches; Polaroid copy.Handwritten on verso: 'Nichols 15b'
- Georgia O'Keeffe's Abiquiu House, Snake Skeleton and Rocks, 1980; 2006.6.524; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 7 15/16 x 10 1/16 inches; Polaroid copy.Handwritten on verso: 'Nichols 16b'
- Abiquiu Plaza, circa 1915-1920; 2006.6.525; 1 Photographic Prints copy print 5 1/8 x 7 inches; Handwritten on verso: Plaza Abiquiu,New Mexico ca 1915-20Stamp on verso: "NOTICE: This photograph is for study purposes only. It must not be reproduced in any form or publicly exhibited in any way without written permission from the owner and must be accompanied by these required credit lines: Photo by Courtesy Museum of New Mexico Neg. No." Handwritten on verso: "13698 PARKHURST 1" "Plaza Abiquiu,New Mexico ca 1915-20" "T. Harmon Parkhurst 13698"
- Georgia O'Keeffe's Ghost Ranch House, Exterior, 1980; 2006.6.553; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 7 15/16 x 10 inches; Polaroid copy.Handwritten on verso: 'Nichols 20b'
- Georgia O'Keeffe's Ghost Ranch House, Patio, 1980; 2006.6.554; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 7 15/16 x 9 15/16 inches; Polaroid copy.Handwritten on verso: 'Nichols 17b'
- Georgia O'Keeffe's Ghost Ranch House, Landscape, 1980; 2006.6.555; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 7 15/16 x 10 inches; Polaroid copy.Handwritten on verso: 'Nichols 18b'
- Georgia O'Keeffe's Ghost Ranch House, Exterior, 1980; 2006.6.556; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 7 15/16 x 10 1/16 inches; Polaroid copy.Handwritten on verso: 'Nichols 19b'
- Pedernal, 1980; 2006.6.557; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 7 15/16 x 9 15/16 inches; Handwritten on verso: 'Sheila Tryk'
- Georgia O'Keeffe, 1903; 2006.6.706; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 1 3/4 x 3 1/2 inches; Framed. Handwritten on verso: Georgia T. O'KeeffeHandwritten on verso: 'Georgia T. O'Keeffe'
  Head shot portrait of Georgia O'Keeffe as a young woman - sixteen years old, quarter length view ( head and shoulders); hair pulled back from face wearing a white high neck dress with lace, face looking slightly to the side and down, photograph displayed in original dark green/gray paper oval mount.
- Georgia O'Keeffe, 1903; 2006.6.707; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 3 5/8 x 1 7/8 inches; Handwritten on verso: Age 16 Georgia O'KeeffeEngraved on recto: "H. Hexelberg" "WILLIAMSBURG. VA." Handwritten on verso: 'R" "Age 16 Georgia O'Keeffe" "WISCONSIN 2" "1444"
  Head shot portrait of Georgia O'Keeffe as a young woman - sixteen years old, quarter length view ( head and shoulders); hair pulled back from face wearing a white high neck dress with lace, face looking slightly to the side and down, photograph displayed in original dark green/gray paper oval mount
- Georgia O'Keeffe at University of Virginia, 1912-1916; 2006.6.708; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 3 3 /16 x 2 5/16 inches; Handwritten on verso: Miss O'Keeffe. Georgia Univ. of VirginiaHandwritten on verso: 'Miss O'Kefe' 'F429' 'Georgia Univ. of Virginia' 'R. OKeeffe'
- Georgia O'Keeffe and Family, circa 1906; 2006.6.709; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 2 7/8 x 5 1/16 inches; Handwritten on verso: Georgia under hammock. Madison, Wisc. 1917? Charlottesville (???) 1916?Handwritten on verso: 'F418' 'Georgia- under hammock Madison, Wisc. 1917 (?) Charlottesville (???) 1916?' '59' is circled
  Ida O'Keeffe is in hammock with hat. Georgia O'Keeffe is below.
- Georgia O'Keeffe and Family, circa 1906; 2006.6.710; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 3 1/8 x 5 7/16 inches; Handwritten on verso: Visit to Wisc - 1913?Handwritten on verso: 'R O'Keeffe' 'Visit to Wisc. - 1913?' 'F419'
- Georgia O'Keeffe at University of Virginia, 1912-1916; 2006.6.711; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 5 1/8 x 3 inches; Framed. Handwritten on verso: Georgia O'Keeffe. Charlottesville, Va. ? Visit to Wisconsin - 1913? [Some handwriting has been crossed out.]Handwritten on verso: 'Charlottesville 1913?'
- Georgia O'Keeffe at University of Virginia, 1912-1916; 2006.6.712; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 2 1/8 x 1 7/16 inches; Handwritten on verso: Charlottesville. Wisc. 1913? (visit to) R. O'Keeffe [Some handwriting has been crossed out.]Handwritten on verso: 'Georgia O'Keeffe Charlottesville, Va' 'R.O'Keefe' 'F426' Though there are some cross-outs?